var questionArray = [
{question:"how much is 8+7 ?",
a:"9",
b:"11",
c:"15",
d:"17",
answer:"15",

},
{question:"how much is 20-9 ?",
a:"21",
b:"11",
c:"12",
d:"19",
answer:"11"
},
{question:"how much is 6x9?",
a:"67",
b:"78",
c:"57",
d:"54",
answer:"54"
},
{question:"how much is 50:5?",
a:"10",
b:"15",
c:"20",
d:"5",
answer:"10"
},
{question:"how much is (6+4)-5?",
a:"10",
b:"6",
c:"20",
d:"5",
answer:"5"
},
{question:"how much is (10-7)+4?",
a:"7",
b:"15",
c:"20",
d:"8",
answer:"7"
},
{question:"how much is (9+3)-4?",
a:"10",
b:"8",
c:"20",
d:"9",
answer:"8"
},
{question:"how much is 2(3+5)?",
a:"16",
b:"13",
c:"20",
d:"17",
answer:"16"
},
{question:"how much is 3(9-2)?",
a:"13",
b:"15",
c:"21",
d:"25",
answer:"21"
},
{question:"how much is 5x6+6x2 ?",
a:"39",
b:"42",
c:"35",
d:"25",
answer:"42"
},
{question:"how much is 4x3-3x2 ?",
a:"15",
b:"6",
c:"12",
d:"9",
answer:"6"
},
{question:"how much is 10:2+8:4 ?",
a:"18",
b:"9",
c:"4",
d:"7",
answer:"7"
},
{question:"how much is 5(4+2)+2(3+5) ?",
a:"46",
b:"34",
c:"56",
d:"32",
answer:"46"
},
{question:"how much is 2(3+4)-3(4-2) ?",
a:"16",
b:"8",
c:"9",
d:"10",
answer:"8"
},
{question:"how much is (2+4)(3+2)?",
a:"14",
b:"36",
c:"45",
d:"30",
answer:"30"

}]